var questions = {
    america: {
        title: "America",
        first: {
            question: "This city is the largest in America",
            answer:  "New York"
        },
        second: {
            question: "The first president of the United States",
            answer: "George Washington"            
        },
        third:  {
            question: "The capital city of America",
            answer: "Washington, D.C."
        },
        fourth: {
            question: "This is the largest state in the continental United States",
            answer: "Alaska"
        },
        fifth: {
            question: "This is the smallest state in the United States",
            answer: "Rhode Island"
        }
    },
    rome:  {
        title: "Rome",
        first: {
            question: "The richest Roman in history",
            answer: "Crassus"
        },
        second: {
            question: "Overthrew the Roman republic",
            answer: "Gaius Julius Caesar"
        },
        third: {
            question: "Carthaginian that entered Italy",
            answer: "Hannible"
        },
        fourth: {
            question: "Defeated Hannible in Africa",
            answer: "Scipio Africanus"
        },
        fifth: {
            question: "First Roman emperor",
            answer: "Augustus"
        }
    }
}